[Music]
I know you're very busy
let me make it easy for you first of all
most likely even our Google travel
insurance then you're gonna go to Bali
for the heart or you'll go to HDFC and I
see you directly let's local taxi as
your comparison of HDR see all those ICS
here rum bar for booking of travel
introduced for this
experiment let's just consider ending
[Music]
so first of all the new Google app for
HD ICCA Lombard and travel insurance
click on the speed and you're free to
invert and for this clicks go HTC will
teach this if you're traveling to the
future
click on buy now and it just opens up in
a new page select your age and click
continue then you will reach here
whereas in Isis here you have to select
a country first and the date let's just
eat
[Music]
[Applause]
entering your age it's an apples to
apples comparison something like a
through our it which we are having the
steam please selected as we have
selected over your okay I'm gonna leave
you some one thing about requires to be
added and part of the friends in
policies I'm going to opt run give the
phone numbers and so let's just continue
with the demonstration to understand the
comparison like you might see over your
after now you see gold and platinum you
can see that you can choose amount of
power
[Music]
which are beautiful because you're
getting more amount of coverage but this
will be subjective on your preferences
and here you can clearly see that the
more the number of covers which are
entering Isis here whereas as you see
the event it with a different look and
feel which I am more of big fan of at
the start but once you understand that
this couch all of that and just like
this
apart rather than doing side-by-side on
the first page there went on horizontal
but there is an ad to compare button
which will compare now and then you will
have the amount of the top they want you
to buy the policy as well as possible so
the big Buy button man you can see the
difference and then you can decide on
how much cover you're going to take and
then you know how much covering all the
key whereas an ICICI you can clearly
just see the cow all complete up and the
summit's in Incheon where as a policy
bazaar you will see that there are just
too many amount of too many policies for
the same amount some insured and ready
for inside and see
is that the government is not acting you
just can't think of oh my gosh and
[Music]
about marriage initiative is the wedding
Mary attack them from Baku
I see NCI
five lakhs 5 like University whereas you
get 24 covers in the platinum fact in
ICICI whereas in NTSC you get quite
limited coverage what are the extras
let's look at the extras probably
this one is an extra this is an extra
little nod include an HDFC but it is
updated we will actually in the fire if
not but as soon as you understand what
all is covered I would again recommend
you who for dedicated plans
[Music]
so thankfully you don't have to enter
your full number and policy bizarre fun
by the way you will have to and you will
start getting messages the moment you
enter your number
first hired on as yet see but there are
less amount of covers but you can say
that you might not require these
additional covers anyways they might not
be useful to you and then you can just
choose on EDS
[Music]
okay the recession expired that that's
revived session actually my experimental
experimental session never expires in
nineteen so that's how long the child
can always click on edit and changed or
dips in select by country as well
[Music]
that's at the bottom JSC
let's start again
[Music]
try to see what happens as you can see
you already thought that this is cute
laughs but there's a country is attacked
the more hired plan the higher the tax
you will have to pay let's just check it
with the pattern about of
[Music]
so you enter all the details again just
to like if you cancel one to 80% GST
will be charged versus on ICICI the GST
is inclusive I just made a purchase
that's fine over with us the GST is
included and in the fact that you see
over your voices when you see an HDFC fo
GS to the modern food and the track
enter the narrow detention slip on next
let's descend
hypothetical news
[Music]
hey something's buggy in the system okay
so you have to click on it and then
automatically populates this it's not
[Music]
right
[Applause]
[Music]
so they expect us to start again they
actually expect us to start and then I
back let go and start again
oh great agency wants us to do extra
work this because you made a fuss
[Music]
when why advances let me check
what policies are there
once you get this it's pasta
[Music]
let's proceed on the checkout choose
your one gold or platinum
once you fill in the details click on
next for the passenger one
and other traveler deals now passenger
one passenger to has at me P as you can
see the prices are including taxes now
you have to decided the policy right you
want to buy you can make the payment and
you will get your policy you will
receive SMS and email you you might also
receive a confirmation
[Music]
we are that the comparison you notice
where we have to end this
[Music]